[ Dee ]
What were you even doing
in that crawl space, Charlie?
[ Charlie ]
Well, for starters,
I was minding my own business.
I was also trying to do
a little light reading.
Then I was putting
some cheese in the rat traps.
You were putting the cheese
in the rat traps?
- Yes!
Can I smell your mouth?
- Why?
You were eating
the cheese, weren't you,
out of the rat traps?
No-- Well, yes.
I was eating
the old cheese to test it,
see why the rats
weren't eating it.
Why are you always
doing such weird things?
- I do weird things?
Name another thing
that you think is weird!
Well, I caught you stealing
a bunch of coins out of
the fountain at Logan Circle.
I was acquiring a little bit
of cash to pay my spy, Dee.
- Why do you have a spy?
To spy on the waitress!
Of course I have a spy!
- Is that normal to you?
Shut up and give me
my book back please!
- No!
Hey, guys.
What book you keep
going on about?
- It's nothing.
You don't need to see it.
- Oh, my God.
Whoa. These are my--
These are my memoirs.
Charlie, you found my book.
I wrote a memoirs.
Hey, guys!
Charlie found my memoirs!
- Your memoirs?
- I've been keeping track
of all my sexual exploits,
and I was gonna unleash them
on the world in a fiery blaze
of eroticism.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down a second, Dennis.
[ Chuckles ] You wrote a book?
Well, it's more of
a tale of redemption told
through my erotic travels.
- Giddyap, man. That's amazing!
- That's good stuff, right?
Yeah.
But then one day
the book just sort of
went mysteriously missing.
- Charlie, what the hell
were you doing with it?
- Well, since he can't read,
I'm guessing
he was masturbating
to your pictures.
God damn! Jackin' off to my--
- God, no!
That is not at all--
What are you doing to me?
Why are you doing this?
You've been riding me.
Now you're
accusing me of things.
You just don't get it.
You don't know why I do
the things that I do.
It's nuts.
You don't know
how hard I got it.
- Got it pretty tough?
Your life is pretty hard?
- I tell you what.
How'd you like
to walk a mile in my shoes?
Try your old buddy Charlie
on for size.
You want me to walk a mile
in your shoes, 'cause I can't
handle your big, tough life?
- I will. That sounds fine
to me. I will do that.
Oh, my God! Shut up!
Dennis, what's the name
of this book?
Ah.
"Dennis Reynolds:
An Erotic Life."
♪
♪♪
"I removed my robe
and stood before her,
"taut, nubile, proud.
"She was much, much older
than me,
"but her breasts were awesome.
I felt reborn, baptized
in erotic majesty."
- Ooh!
- [ Laugh ]
Yeah!
This is some sweet smut!
I'm all boned-up over here.
- Me too.
Dennis, we should try
and sell this book.
Personal memoirs
are huge right now.
Yeah, yeah, no. I'm gonna
sell the book,
but I'm not gonna
let you guys be involved.
Because every time you're
involved you get all excited
about something,
and then you give up
the minute we hit
the first speed bump.
You need us, Dennis.
You're gonna need
some legal help.
Legal help?
Bro, half the stories
you just read us
are total bullshit.
They're not bullshit.
What are you saying?
Dennis, you were never
the personal sexual adviser
to Jon Bon Jovi.
And you never woke up
in a rehab facility
with the wounds of Christ...
miraculously appearing
on your hands and feet.
Yeah, man, but I banged
that girl in the fountain.
That story was true--
the hot dogs, the oatmeal,
everything.
Dude, you don't want to end up
like that Million Little Pieces
guy. All right?
Oprah made him look
like a total dick.
Oh, that guy was a turd.
I mean, come on.
Just take some
of those stories out.
No, see, Frank, he can't take
those stories out.
That's the rub.
That's why he needs us.
Because the public loves
those crazy celebrity stories
and rehab shit.
Okay, so what are you thinking?
I'm thinking we take some
of the really good stories--
you know, the Jon Bon Jovi,
the Christ-wound stigmatas--
and we re-create them.
We make them true
so that people can't prove
that they didn't happen.
Re-create some
of the better stories in here
and then we have proof.
Yes!
Holy shit, man.
That's a good idea.
Now, first things first.
We gotta figure out how
to get you in a rehab.
Charlie, do I really
have to sleep here?
If you're gonna
walk a mile in my shoes,
this is a pretty big part
of that mile,
don't you think?
Now here. Put these on.
No. I don't want to wear one
of your dirty sleeping outfits.
I'm sorry, but my "outfits,"
as you like to call them,
serve a very specific purpose.
This isn't just for fun.
I don't have any heating ducts
in this apartment.
It gets freezing in here
at night, all right?
Now, in case you have
to pee-pee, I got this
for you, all right?
Oh, my God!
Goddamn it! Frank was
supposed to empty that!
Charlie, no wonder
it reeks in here!
You have open cans
of pee everywhere!
But you do not
want to use that bathroom! Okay,
now eat one of these, all right?
You're gonna wanna
huff a little glue
and drink some beer.
This is cat food, Charlie.
Well, Dee,
I can't explain it!
There's some sort
of weird chemical reaction
that happens...
when you combine cat food,
beer and glue.
It makes you feel
extremely sick and tired,
and you're able to fall asleep.
Why would I want
to make myself
extremely sick and tired?
'Cause there's gonna be
about 50 cats howling outside
that window all night long,
and you have no idea
how loud 50 cats can be.
Maybe there wouldn't be cats
surrounding your building...
if you didn't have open cans
of cat food everywhere!
I have 50 cats howling
outside my window,
because I have 10,000 rats
running around my building!
Okay? I'm not an idiot!
Stop yelling.
You're spitting cat food on me.
There's a reason to do
the things that I-- Oh.
[ Stomach Rumbling ]
I don't feel good.
[ Cat Meows ]
And it's starting right on time.
If I were you, I'd start
wolfin' that shit down.
I gotta go to sleep.
Oh, I'm not
feeling good at all.
[ Grunting ]
[ Cats Meowing ]
[ Stomachs Gurgling ]
[ Loud Meowing ]
[ Exhales Forcefully ]
[ Man, Woman Arguing,
Indistinct ]
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
[ Man ]
♪ You cast a spell on me
I was blind but now I see ♪
♪♪ [ Fades ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Women Arguing, Indistinct ]
Come play with us forever
and ever and ever...
and ever.
[ Screams ]
[ Urinating ]
Ocupado.
[ Gasps ]
Mmm. All gone. All gone.
[ Gags ]
Wake up! Let's go!
Time to start the day.
What?
Time to get up!
Charlie! Oh, God!
Oh, God!
There's evil twins
in the hallway
and a twitching junkie--
What? How much of
that glue did you huff?
- I don't know.
As much as you did.
- As much as me?
Really? [ Chuckles ]
Well, that's probably
way too much glue for you, Dee.
Hey, check it out.
You just had yourself
a glue O.D.
Those are pretty regular
in my life.
Don't do too much glue
or your night sucks.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on a second.
You're saying that your life
is so terrible because you eat
rat cheese and cat food...
and huff glue all day long?
Uh, yeah!
Those aren't real problems,
Charlie.
What do you mean,
they're not real problems?
You make those problems up!
You choose to do that stuff!
Those are solutions
to problems!
Oh, my God.
You know what?
Hold on a second.
We're gonna turn the tables
here.
You're gonna walk
a mile in my shoes now,
and you're gonna see what it's
like to live in the real world
and have actual problems!
Okay. You got some glue
on your face though.
You might want
to wash that off.
Oh, goddamn it.
Okay, plan is simple.
You're gonna hang out at
the rehab facility
for a couple of days...
while we get the ball
rolling with Bon Jovi.
Uh, yeah.
I gotta say I'm a little
skeptical about you guys...
being able to get in touch
with Jon Bon Jovi.
What? What do you mean?
He's from New Jersey.
[ Fingers Snap ]
Piece of cake.
Have a little faith
in us please.
Plus, it's easy.
We just get you into
a room with him,
snap a couple of photos,
we got proof.
Bing, bang, boom. We're done.
Now, let's talk stigmatas.
That's it, huh?
Mmm.
Uh, right.
Do we have
to do the stigmatas?
You know this publisher is gonna
have a fact checker, right?
Yeah.
You don't want to end up like
the Million Little Pieces guy,
do you?
I brought a nail gun.
Oh, is that
what that is?
Yeah.
No, no. Look, you're not
gonna shoot nails in me.
No. I think a couple
of severe burns from the cigar
is what's gonna do the trick.
What?
No, you need
deep wounds.
No, wait.
This'll give you
deep wounds.
Hold on a second! No!
I can get these
pretty deep.
Nobody's gonna burn me
or shoot me full of nails!
Dennis, calm down!
You focus on your art,
okay?
Frank and I will handle
all the business end of things.
Hang on a second.
If you guys really
want to do the stigmata--
Okay. Good work, Frank.
I think we should just probably
leave the body right here.
Yeah, we can leave him here.
In the morning they'll
come out and find him.
All right,
give me his hands.
Yo.
[ Man ]
I don't go to a therapist.
I just go to bars.
If you walk up to
the nearest drunk guy
and bump him from behind,
he always turns around
and goes, "Hey, man.
What's your problem?"
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Chuckles ]
This guy is great.
Do you come here every night?
Every night, huh?
This is great.
Hey, do they have food too?
'Cause I could go for some food.
No, no. No food.
I don't eat
while I'm here.
When do you eat?
I don't.
Why don't you eat dinner, Dee?
You gotta eat dinner sometime.
Because when you perform
your nerves make you
dry heave,
and you better hope you don't
have any food in your stomach.
You're gonna perform?
All right. Now, this next lady
y'all know, because she's here
almost every night.
Let's hope she's got
some new jokes this time.
Everybody put your hands
together for Deandra Reynolds!
[ Applause Smattering ]
Howdy, howdy, howdy.
How's everybody doing tonight?
[ Chuckles Weakly ]
So, you guys,
what's the deal with
those hands-free headsets...
that everybody's wearing
in their ears, right?
[ Gags ]
It's like, "Hey, everybody,
look at me! I'm one part robot
and three parts asshole!"
[ Gagging ]
[ Man ]
Jesus Christ!
[ Exhales Heavily ]
I mean, am I right, or am I--
[ Gags, Coughs ] Screw it!
[ Applause Smattering ]
Wow. Well, at least it was
short and dry this time.
[ Laughing ]
Dee, what are you doing to
yourself? That is terrible.
Why would you do that?
You just gotta put in
your dues, you know?
You gotta take it one step at
a time when you want to be an
actor.
What? This is about being
an actor? Why in God's name are
you still trying to be an actor?
Okay, we all have our hopes
and dreams. You're still trying
to get with the waitress.
I'm still trying to act.
We just do whatever
we need to do.
Oh, is it funny? You better get
ready, guy, 'cause you're next.
Huh?
Let's hear it
for a newcomer here tonight,
Mr. Charlie Kelly!
So, you guys,
you ever eat cheese?
Cheese is a funny thing.
Cheese is a strange thing.
I always wonder, like,
what is cheese?
Where does it--
[ Gagging ]
We gotta figure out
how to get you into rehab.
Let's talk stigmatas.
You need
deep wounds.
No, no, wait.
[ Mac ]
Rehab-- Rehab--
Yo, punk.
Wake up, punk.
Yo, punk!
Ow!
Wake up!
What the hell?
Yeah, you in hell,
all right!
What?
You know what?
My name is Sinbad!
This Sinbad's house!
When you're in Sinbad house,
you're my bitch!
Listen--
[ Sniffs ]
Yeah, you know who that is?
Huh? That's Rob Thomas.
Matchbox 20! Sing a song.
Uh--
Shut up!
Matchbox 20? Eww!
You the man, huh?
You gonna punk him like that?
No, no!
Matterof fact, unleash the fury.
Get his shoe!
What?
Beat his testicles!
No, no, no! Don't beat!
Don't, don't, don't, don't!
Come on. Rob Thomas
and Si-- Sinbad.
Uh, look, man.
I'm pretty confused
about what I'm seeing here.
And I'm in a lot of pain.
Just tell me what's going on.
It's the pain, huh?
My bad. I didn't know
you was hurting like that.
My bad. 'Cause I've hurt
before. You've hurt before.
We all hurt.
So I'm gonna just break it down
now. Introduce myself right.
That was wrong.
I'm Sinbad. There's my
head shot. Autograph for you
a little later on.
And this is Sinbad's house.
[ Shouting ]
And you're my bitch!
I'm gonna
show you how--
[ Door Opens ]
- Everything okay in here?
- Hey, what's up, Jerome? Man,
he keep throwin' his shoe.
- He crazy.
- Let's go. Everybody should
be in bed with the lights off.
We're tryin' to go to sleep.
He keep throwin' shoes at us.
You're about to get me
jacked up, man! Is that
what you're tryin' to do?
Shut up!
Man, I'll poke your eye out!
See this?
This one on you,
and this one on Rob Thomas.
I own both y'all!
Watch your ass, new meat.
All righty then.
See you soon. Bye-bye.
[ Chuckling ]
- Hey, dude.
- I just made a date with that
girlie rock star's people.
- Bon Jovi? Oh!
- Yeah. He owns
the Philadelphia Soul--
the arena football team.
- I just offered to buy it.
- Awesome!
All right, I'm gonna pretend
that I have terminal cancer...
and get him to do
an acoustic set on my deathbed.
Wait. Why would you do that?
You don't have to do that.
No, it's great, bro. Rock stars
do the cancer-kid thing
all the time. Look, Frank!
No!
You got us into a room
with Jovi's people, right?
I'm gonna get us into a room
with Jovi himself!
I'm sorry! That's a stupid idea.
I don't want you to do it.
I already got a bald-cap guy
and everything.
You're just
confusing everything!
There's nothing confusing
about it, Frank!
It's very, very simple!
Shut up!
Shut your big mouth
right now!
I will put my foot down
right now! You are not going
in there with that cancer thing!
I don't care what you say!
So get it out of your head!
Okay. Jesus, dude.
I won't do the cancer thing.
Relax.
So, Mr. Reynolds,
you're interested in buying
our arena football team.
Big time!
But I want to do business
with Mr. Von Joni himself.
Bon Jovi?
Yeah!
Mr. Bovine Joni himself.
I'm offering $40 million
for the team.
Wow. Well, that is
a very generous offer.
But I must admit I'm a little
bit confused about one thing.
What's confusing
about 40 million?
That's a shitload of money.
It is. It is. I'm a little
confused as to why you've chosen
to involve this gentleman here.
Uh-- [ Sighs ]
Well, if I may, I'd like to
explain to you why I'm here.
Uh, ma'am, I am dying
of very terminal cancer,
and I would like to request
a private bedside concert
from Mr. Bon Jovi.
Ahh.
Now, Sambora's presence
is not necessary.
But it would be nice if
he was involved. Question:
Is this a laser pointer?
Yes.
Can I have it?
No.
I'm gonna take it anyway.
Please don't listen
to anything he says.
No, no. No, Frank.
I'll give you $60 million
for the team.
Frank, you-- I got it.
We're talking
about cancer.
We're negotiating!
You're not negotiating shit.
We're onto
the cancer thing now.
That is the way that
it's gonna go from here.
Okay. I'm just gonna
throw this out there.
I don't think you have cancer.
What? What are you
talking about? No, that's chemo.
That's chemotherapy right there.
And for the record,
when you go through chemo,
your beard hair falls out too.
Are you sure?
I asked a lot of people!
I asked my bald-cap guy!
I told you not to do
the cancer thing!
But it was working until you got
in with the bullshit numbers!
Goddamn it!
You know, I'm not even
really bald. I have a full
head of hair. Not like him.
Not only do I consider it
magnificent, I have a sneaking
suspicion it's pretty good.
[ Slurping ]
Hey!
On his eyes.
Shine it on his dick.
Shine it on his dick!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- [ Laughing ]
Look at his dick!
♪♪ [ Cell Phone Ring Tone:
Country ]
Oh, that's me. That's my phone.
My phone is ringing.
Sorry, that's me.
Hey, dude.
Where you been?
I'm in rehab, dude!
Oh, yeah.
Hey, that whole Jovi
thing went south,
so I think we're just gonna
scrap the whole book ordeal.
[ Slurping ]
- What are you talking about?
- [ Beeping ]
I got another call, buddy.
No, no!
No, don't--
Hello?
[ Man ]
Bill, what's happening?
Who are you
looking for?
Bill. Who's this?
Oh, this is Mac.
You got the wrong number.
Oh, my bad.
Yeah. No problem.
What number were you
trying to call?
- Shh!
- ♪♪ [ Cell Phone Ring Tone:
Disco ]
- Hello?
- Frank, you gotta
get me outta here, man!
Where are you?
I'm in rehab,
goddamn it!
Well, I'm in a movie,
and this broad's about
to get naked.
So I gotta go.
No, no, no!
Yeah. No, that's okay.
Yeah, I thought
it was some chick.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to Bill.
And anyway, so--
No, I'm not Bill.
I'm Terry.
Bill?
I'm sorry. No, it's Terry.
Sorry about that, Terry. Anyway,
these cat people hated me--
Terry? What number did he want?
'cause I kept calling
them over and over.
Will you please shut up!
[ Terry ]
Who's that?
I got some dick in
a movie theater giving me shit.
Why you turn around like that?
Yeah. Nice talking
to you. All right.
Call me back.
I'll talk to
you afterwards. Bye.
[ Muttering ]
Give me
the laser pointer.
What a jerk.
I know. Watch this. I'm gonna
do it on the back of his head.
[ Chuckling ]
Bro, you wore
the battery down.
Oh.
Well, how am I supposed
to use it now?
'Cause you-- Jerk!
I'm a jerk?
Yeah.
You're a jerk.
You're walking around with
that bald cap on all day,
and I'm a jerk.
It was expensive. I'm sorry.
I want to get my money's worth.
You're talking to a guy--
Will you please be quiet?
Who talks like this in
the middle of a movie theater?
Hey. Hey, you don't know
how hard I got it, pal.
You don't know
how tough it is bein' me.
What?
It's not that tough to be you,
Frank. What is so difficult
about your life?
Yeah, try walkin' a mile
in my shoes once in a while
and then talk to me.
[ Man In Film ]
Would you allow me
to show you my--
[ Thinking ]
Our eyes locked,
our hands touched,
and she whispered in my ear,
"Dude, your balls
totally rule."
[ Door Opens ]
[ Sinbad ]
What the hell you think
you doing, man?
I heard about this shit!
It's gonna stop!
Take his book, Rob!
Whoa, whoa, wait!
[ Yelping ]
Come on. I was just
in the middle of some
really erotic stuff.
Yeah, I heard about that shit.
You trying to write memoirs
and erotic shit.
Know what?
You don't write it, bitch!
I'll write it!
What is your problem, Sinbad?
Think you Jesus?
You think you Jesus?
Ain't no Jesus here
'cept me! I'm Jesus!
What the hell, man?
You stole my thing!
No, no. My thing is bigger.
Rule of the land.
Big is my thing now.
Took it. Bam! Mine!
Fine. But what does Rob Thomas
have to do with any of this?
You know Rob-- You know what
he's got to do with it?
He do whatever I tell him do,
because he's my bitch, bitch!
Let's get out of here.
We're gonna read some smut.
Come on, man.
Shut up. Give it to him.
Give it-- No, I'm playing!
[ Laughs ]
[ Door Closes ]
I gotta get outta here.
This is my day,
and this is where I come
at the end of the day...
before I head off to Paddy's.
Why do you come to the fountain?
The fountain's my thing.
Well, I'll tell you why
I come to the fountain.
I come here every single day
to throw money into this thing
to wish for a better life.
Money that you
apparently steal for spies!
Okay, so essentially, Charlie,
you're stealing my dreams!
- If you don't mind, I'm gonna
get those dreams back now.
- No, those are my spy coins.
That's my money anyway!
You can't have that!
How is that your money?
It's itchy. This is what I
gotta go through to get laid.
Frank, shut up!
You're just pissed off,
'cause I pull it off
better than you.
You don't pull it off
better than anything.
You better not lose your hair,
'cause you're an ugly bald man.
Not as ugly as you, bitch.
Ah!
What are we doing here?
This is the time of day
when I come to the fountain.
Why?
When I was a kid
I used to swim in this fountain.
A bunch of bullies
kicked me out.
So I wait until this
time of day and come back
and piss in the fountain.
I've been pissin'
in the fountain
for 50 years.
Well, why are you
still pissing in it?
To get back at their kids!
-Greedy, greedy! Greedy Dee!
-You can't have a good life
without your dreams!
Is that Dee and Charlie?
Hey, guys, what are you doing?
What the hell?
These are my dreams!
They mean something to me!
It's anyone's coins!
Yo, Charlie and Dee!
[ Shouting, Arguing ]
Deandra!
What are you doing?
Dee!
I'm taking my dreams back!
What are you guys doing?
Frank's gonna piss
in the fountain.
I do it every day.
Hey, I like
your haircut, man.
What's going on up here?
You can't tell.
Charlie, it's a bald cap.
It's not even real!
You can't tell, huh?
Oh, my God!
[ Charlie ] That's awesome!
[ Dee ]
No, you can you can tell.
- [ Charlie ] You say you were
gonna piss in the fountain?
- You're in it.
Hey, Dennis!
What's up, buddy?
Come here!
What you doing?
Hey, guys.
Huh?
I use this fountain
for its healing powers.
Plus, it does wonders for my
skin. [ Gibberish ] But that's
not important right now!
- You're not gonna believe this.
Sinbad was trying to kill me!
- What?
Yeah, Sinbad the comedian.
He was in the rehab center.
He was trying to kill me.
And then Rob Thomas,
the lead singer of Matchbox 20?
He was in there too.
- Is any of that making sense?
- No.
Uh, time-time out, time
out, time out. Did you
or did you not meet Sinbad?
Yeah. I met Sinbad. But--
Can you prove
that stuff?
Oh, yeah.
This happened just moments ago!
Boom!
Memoir's back on.
Me!
Rob Thomas is a douche bag, but
the public eats that shit up!
Yeah!
The memoirs thing is done!
We gotta go back
to that rehab.
No, no!
We can't go back there!
That's too dangerous!
No, we have to prove it.
We gotta take photos.
We have to sign documents.
- Dude, I'm a huge Sinbad fan!
- Sinbad is not the man
that you think he is, Charlie!
We'll take care of you.
We'll watch your back.
I am not going back!
I'd like to meet him.
I hope he's wearing something
made out of windbreaker.
Okay, guys. This is it.
[ Mac ]
What the hell is this?
It's the rehab center.
That's not the rehab center.
That's the rehab center.
Well, this is where
they brought me after
you guys dropped me off.
Everybody, you gotta
stay close to me, okay?
You have to protect me,
because like most comedians
Sinbad is very angry
on the inside.
Come on. Come on!
Do you think he'll, like,
autograph my shirt? Or, like--
He will autograph your face
until it is bloody to a pulp.
Now come on!
So, like--
like what is this place, dude?
[ Door Closes ]
Hey!
Oh, hell, no!
We told you not
to come back here,
freak!
Wh-Where's Sinbad?
Oh, you call me Sinbad
one more time,
I'm gonna knock you out.
- What the hell
is going on here?
- This dude broke in here,
and has been running around
ranting and raving
about memoirs and Sinbad!
So--
So you lied to us,
Dennis?
No, I didn't lie.
No, I swear to God.
This was all real.
- Sinbad was here, I swear!
- That's it.
I'm calling the cops.
You thought that
dude was Sinbad.
This guy?
Maybe that blow to the head
did a little more damage
than we thought.
That's not Sinbad, dude!
I know that's
not Sinbad!
Is this some sort
of sick fantasy?
No, it's not a fantasy!
I didn't make it up!
Sinbad was here! I swear!
Well, guess what, guy?
The memoir is dead again!
I can't believe
you didn't meet Sinbad!
Do you even realize how excited
I was to meet Sinbad!
Sinbad's a hilarious comedian.
Goddamn it.
Son of a bitch.
That guy is like some dude
in green pants.
I don't even see how
this could be happening.
It all seemed so real.
[ Door Closes ]
I need to see a doctor.
Psst.
No, you don't, bitch!
- Wake up! Yeah,
you in hell all right!
- Ow!
- Oh, what the hell, man?
- Hell, no!
You call me Sinbad
one more time--
Yeah. I should definitely
see a doctor.
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]